{"data":[{"question":"Seismology has not reached yet the stage where earthquakes can be foretold with a great  deal of accuracy. \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"reached yet ","b":"stage ","c":"be foretold ","d":"accuracy","answer":"1","explain":"- Reached yet-> reached","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Medical research indicates but large amounts of histamines can be responsible for colds, hay fever, and other respiratory reactions.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"but ","b":"large amounts ","c":"can be ","d":"colds","answer":"1","explain":"- But-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Precisely because photographs ''are produced by mechanical devices, a camera's images now seem  to some artists the perfect means for expression the modern era.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are produced ","b":"mechanical ","c":"the perfect ","d":"for expression ","answer":"4","explain":"-> For expression-> to expressing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The Swiss admit to running work camps for refugees during the war, but deny whether they were specifically designed to victimize Jews.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to running ","b":"but ","c":"whether ","d":"specifically ","answer":"3","explain":"- Whether-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"He was stopped each dozen yards by friends who wanted to congratulate him.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"each ","b":"yards ","c":"wanted to ","d":"him","answer":"1","explain":"- Each-> every","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"All objects are composed of many molecules and the  force of gravity pulls on every of  them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are composed ","b":"force ","c":"pulls ","d":"every ","answer":"4","explain":"- Every-> each","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"One or the other of the secretaries have to attend the meeting. But both of them are  reluctant to do so.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"One or the other ","b":"of the ","c":"have to ","d":"both of them ","answer":"3","explain":"- Have to-> has to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Wagner and Strauss were such good friends that they frequently exchanged gifts with one another.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"such ","b":"that ","c":"frequently ","d":"with one another","answer":"4","explain":"- One another-> each other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Culture and society are so interdependent that they do not occur without each another.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Culture ","b":"society ","c":"occur ","d":"another","answer":"4","explain":"- Another-> other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The seventeenth century was one in that many significant advances were made in both science and philosophy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"one ","b":"in that ","c":"were ","d":"in both ","answer":"2","explain":"- In that-> in which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}